// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q028: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Please submit your survey form as soon as possible ------ your responses can be included in the survey results.',
      choices: ['even if', 'therefore', 'so that', 'because of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['so that'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q271',
    },
    {
      question: 'Mougey Corporation ------ a new personnel system for all employees by the end of this fall.',
      choices: ['has introduced', 'will be introducing', 'was introducing', 'will be introduced'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['will be introducing'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q272',
    },
    {
      question: '------ the five employees eligible for promotion, Ms. Oswald is seen as the most promising.',
      choices: ['With', 'For', 'Toward', 'Of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Of'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q273',
    },
    {
      question: '------ manufacturing processes have resulted in a 30% increase in productivity.',
      choices: ['Improving', 'To improve', 'Improved', 'Improve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Improved'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q274',
    },
    {
      question: 'It is difficult to determine the cost of production because the prices of raw materials are ------ changing.',
      choices: ['constantly', 'formerly', 'respectively', 'initially'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['constantly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q275',
    },
    {
      question: 'This banquet hall can ------ up to 200 people, and reservations can be made six months prior to the event.',
      choices: ['generate', 'accommodate', 'achieve', 'enhance'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['accommodate'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q276',
    },
    {
      question: '------ rooms in our hotel have Wi-Fi access and are equipped with a charger for smartphones.',
      choices: ['Every', 'Each', 'Almost', 'All'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['All'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q277',
    },
    {
      question: 'Riverdale Fresh Market sells locally grown produce at ------ prices.',
      choices: ['thorough', 'eligible', 'reasonable', 'proficient'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['reasonable'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q278',
    },
    {
      question: 'Advances in communication technology allow workers to work from home ------.',
      choices: ['easier', 'ease', 'more easily', 'easiest'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['more easily'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q279',
    },
    {
      question: '------ being lightweight, this laptop has a longer-lasting battery than other models.',
      choices: ['In addition', 'As well', 'Besides', 'Now that'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Besides'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題271-280/#q280',
    },
  ],
}